<item>
	<title>Dear Pfizer:</title>
	<link>http://homefornow.us/dear-pfizer</link>
	<pubDate>Thu Sep 06 20:51:54 -0700 2012</pubDate>
	
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Morgan Estes]]></dc:creator>
	
	

	<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://homefornow.us/dear-pfizer</guid>
	<description></description>
	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><div class='p_embed p_image_embed'>
<a href="http://getfile5.posterous.com/getfile/files.posterous.com/homefornow/buuBsEJkvDvbrryuvAqgHqenFgBAbonbwoJHsrzgHxhtsgHamzfnjtyxjzCh/1201020034.jpg"><img alt="1201020034" src="http://getfile5.posterous.com/getfile/files.posterous.com/homefornow/buuBsEJkvDvbrryuvAqgHqenFgBAbonbwoJHsrzgHxhtsgHamzfnjtyxjzCh/1201020034.jpg" /></a>
</div>
</p>Pfizer, this is my plea to you concerning your infant's Advil. Please take inspiration (read: steal heavily) from your Tylenol-ish counterparts and change your bottle to one that doesn't make me have to hose of the sticky mess each time I have to cajole my daughter into taking medicine.<p>Sincerely,</p><p>A dad whose already frazzled with a sick baby and who doesn't want to deal with your sticky mess.</p><p>Pictured: at left is the glass bottle containing a sticky solution of Advil along with the syringe that I must stick all the way into the bottle to get a dose. At right is the Walgreens brand of acetaminophen, with the nice, clean syringe that makes it much easier to dose. All three brands of acetaminophen we've used have the same system just waiting to be copied by the Advil packaging team.</p>]]></content:encoded>
	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[Pfizer, this is my plea to you concerning your infant's Advil. Please take inspiration (read: steal heavily) from your Tylenol-ish counterparts and change your bottle to one that doesn't make me have to hose of the sticky mess each time I have to ...]]></excerpt:encoded>	

	<wp:post_date>Thu Sep 06 20:51:54 -0700 2012</wp:post_date>
	<wp:post_date_gmt>Thu Sep 06 20:51:54 -0700 2012</wp:post_date_gmt>
	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
	<wp:post_id>159477356</wp:post_id>
	<wp:post_name>dear-pfizer</wp:post_name>
	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>

	
</item>
