<item>
	<title>Standing</title>
	<link>http://homefornow.us/standing</link>
	<pubDate>Thu Oct 25 19:38:42 -0700 2012</pubDate>
	
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[HomeForNow]]></dc:creator>
	
	

	<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://homefornow.us/standing</guid>
	<description></description>
	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><div class='p_embed p_image_embed'>
<a href="http://getfile9.posterous.com/getfile/files.posterous.com/homefornow/yhsraIlrkwqkrjHHblgFgIJuzGqsIstkdpyJujdtmmtIgApsbHxpsujlBnEd/-231955683.jpg"><img alt="-231955683" src="http://getfile9.posterous.com/getfile/files.posterous.com/homefornow/yhsraIlrkwqkrjHHblgFgIJuzGqsIstkdpyJujdtmmtIgApsbHxpsujlBnEd/-231955683.jpg" /></a>
<a href="http://getfile3.posterous.com/getfile/files.posterous.com/homefornow/uJdDnFcHxegehgAHctktqcbCzpannGJCwhfnfdukjdmzHvicJxueCqpnirpy/-231032162.jpg"><img alt="-231032162" src="http://getfile3.posterous.com/getfile/files.posterous.com/homefornow/uJdDnFcHxegehgAHctktqcbCzpannGJCwhfnfdukjdmzHvicJxueCqpnirpy/-231032162.jpg" /></a>
</div>
</p>We took part in OC's Trick or Treat Night tonight. For our first 5 years here I was responsible for two dorms of mostly college sophomores who participated in handing out candy to the children that came. It was always a crazy night - fun, but crazy. We usually had over 300 costumed kids come through. <p>Tonight we got to experience receiving the candy rather than handing it out. </p><p>Joanna was decked out in a ladybug costume we got from someone a while back. She grabbed her treat bucket (I got a happy meal at McDonald's for my lunch today so we'd have a bucket) and hung on to it the whole time as fun college students dropped in pieces of candy. </p><p>Just after taking the picture with our sweet friends from church she stood on her own for the longest things she has yet. Yes, she had a baby doll in one hand and a treat bucket in the other, but she just stood there as we looked on in amazement. </p><p>What a fun night seeing lots of friends from our time he on Edmond. It's fun being home here in Edmond and at OC.</p>]]></content:encoded>
	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[We took part in OC's Trick or Treat Night tonight. For our first 5 years here I was responsible for two dorms of mostly college sophomores who participated in handing out candy to the children that came. It was always a crazy night - fun, but craz...]]></excerpt:encoded>	

	<wp:post_date>Thu Oct 25 19:38:42 -0700 2012</wp:post_date>
	<wp:post_date_gmt>Thu Oct 25 19:38:42 -0700 2012</wp:post_date_gmt>
	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
	<wp:post_id>166550199</wp:post_id>
	<wp:post_name>standing</wp:post_name>
	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>

	
</item>
