<item>
	<title>A WHOLE six weeks?!</title>
	<link>http://homefornow.us/a-whole-six-weeks</link>
	<pubDate>Sun Oct 16 16:12:00 -0700 2011</pubDate>
	
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Morgan Estes]]></dc:creator>
	
	
		<category domain="tag" nicename="morgan"><![CDATA[morgan]]></category>
	
		<category domain="tag" nicename="work"><![CDATA[work]]></category>
	

	<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://homefornow.us/a-whole-six-weeks</guid>
	<description></description>
	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="direction: ltr;">When I started my current position with the </span><a href="http://www.okbar.org/" style="direction: ltr;">Oklahoma Bar Association</a><span style="direction: ltr;"> back in February 2009, one of the benefits mentioned was the geat parental leave policy. Not intending to have kids, I didn't think much of it. I may have even had a snarky reply that it was one benefit I'd never use.</span></p>
<p>Now, 2.5 years later, I am really thankful for it. I get <strong>six weeks</strong> of paid parental leave to be at home with Jessica and Joanna. Six weeks to help care for Jessica (who has just undergone major surgery) and Joanna (who is freaking out in this new world).</p>
<p>Folks seem absolutely amazed that my work gives me this much time off. Some are even more surprised that I'm taking it! I say that this is probably the best time for me <em>to</em>&nbsp;take off. Personally, it's important to me and my family; professionally, it's reassuring to know that the ship still sails without me and I can trust the folks who are backing me up. Winning all around!</p>
<p>The work is challenging. The b<span style="direction: ltr;">enefits: outstanding.</span></p>]]></content:encoded>
	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[When I started my current position with the Oklahoma Bar Association back in February 2009, one of the benefits mentioned was the geat parental leave policy. Not intending to have kids, I didn't think much of it. I may have even had a snarky reply...]]></excerpt:encoded>	

	<wp:post_date>Sun Oct 16 16:12:00 -0700 2011</wp:post_date>
	<wp:post_date_gmt>Sun Oct 16 16:12:00 -0700 2011</wp:post_date_gmt>
	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
	<wp:post_id>75763498</wp:post_id>
	<wp:post_name>a-whole-six-weeks</wp:post_name>
	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>

	
</item>
